>> Jem Young: 当我们把一个服务器的大小叫做 VPS时，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
when we size a server it's called a VPS,
这是虚拟专用服务器
that's a Virtual Private Server.
又因为你操纵它看起来你有一个完整的服务器
Again because when you're manipulating it,
it looks like you have an entire server
但实际上你只有一个盒子的一个盒子，一个服务器的一部分。
to yourself but in reality you just have
a chunk of a box, of a piece of a server.
我一个月可以付五元钱
And I can pay five bucks a month and
您可以获取服务器的块，而不是运行整个服务器。
you get a chunk of a server rather
than having to run an entire server.
只有通过线程技术的优点才能实现这一点。
And this is only possible through
the advantages of the way of threading and
流程隔离和真实操作系统更能实现
process isolation and honestly operating
systems have got better about having
不同进程同时运行。
different processes
running at the same time.
明天我们谈集装箱的时候再谈这个
And we'll talk more about that tomorrow
when we talk about containers and
为什么要用 VPSs 和我们完全的运作方式来改变游戏
why they are game changers in terms
of VPSs and how we wholly run things.
但今天，仅仅是基础，我们就不会变得太复杂了。
But for today, just the basics,
we're not gonna get too complicated.
所以今天我们需要的是购买 VPS。
So today what we're gonna need is
we're gonna need to buy the VPS.
所以基本上我们要买服务器的时间。
So essentially we're
gonna buy server time.
幸运的是，与上次不同，我的引荐链接在这里。
Fortunately, unlike last time,
I have my referral link in here.
因此，如果您使用此 DigitalOcean 引用链接。
So if you use this
DigitalOcean referral link.
你得放进你的信用卡里
You have to put in your credit card.
但你得到的是免费的 50 美元
But what you get is you get
$50 in free credits, and
足够让你的服务器免费运行十个月
that's enough to run your server for
ten months for free.
上次我觉得你花了五美元的钱
So last time, I felt bad cuz you
had spend like five bucks or
用于运行服务器的内容。
something to run a server.
你会得到免费的学分，我获得了免费的学分，所以它是一场双赢的胜利。
You'll get free credits, and I get free
credits so it's kind of a win win.
那就去 DigitalOcean 我送你过去
So go ahead and go to DigitalOcean and
I'll walk you through
你想买哪台服务器到底发生了什么
kind of which server you wanna
buy exactly what's happening.
如果你已经有服务器运行
And if you already have a server running,
可能购买另一个，因为我们希望在正确的安装上使用全新的服务器。
probably buy another one because we want
a fresh server on the right installation.
如果你在 Ubuntu 或 Fedora 的旧版上
If you're on an old version of Ubuntu or
Fedora or something like that,
命令就会有点不同
commands are gonna be
a little bit different.
我要去 DigitalOcean
I'm going to go to DigitalOcean.
>> Jem Young: DigitalOcean ，我登录。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: DigitalOcean account,
I logged in.
> > Jem Young: 所以我给你一分钟的时间来报名。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So I'll give you
a minute to walk through the sign up.
当你通过报名的时候，如果你还没有账户的话，
When you get through the sign up, and
if you don't already have an account,
就会有这样的画面
you'll be presented with
a screen like that.
我们会打电话来的我要启动一个新项目
We'll actually call,
I'm gonna start a new project.
你不必这么做只是为了我的利益
You don't have to do this,
it's just for my sake.
>> Jem Young: 堆栈前端到。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Stack front end to.
> > Jem Young: 没关系，这是教育的目的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's okay,
it's educational purposes.
>> Jem Young: 现在希望你们都在 DigitalOcean 账户上
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So now hopefully you're
all set up on DigitalOcean account.
发放信用卡，提供一些免费的贷款。
Putting credit card,
giving some free credits.
更重要的是我会得到一些免费的贷款
I'll be getting some free
credits more importantly.
如果你想知道为什么选择 DigitalOcean 作为主持人
And if you're wondering why choose
DigitalOcean as the host and
他们在那里有很多人
provider cuz there's a lot of them there.
有 Azure ，有很多不同类型的主机。
There's AWS, there's Azure,
there's lots of different types of hosts.
我选择 DigitalOcean ，因为对我来说，它有最干净的 UI 和最简单的 UI。
I choose DigitalOcean because, to me, it
has the cleanest UI and the simplest UI.
例如，这是我的 Web 站点的 AWS ，它是托管的。
For example, this is AWS for
my website, it's hosted.
所以如果你去爱 WS 你会怎么样
So if you go to AWS you're like, what?
我现在怎么办
What do I do now?
你就喜欢，我需要用 EC2 ，因为 EC2 是它们的虚拟服务器。
And you're like, I need to use an EC2
because EC2 is their virtual servers.
所以你必须提前知道这一点
So you have to know that ahead of time.
然后你就像现在我想开始一个 EC2 的事件我想做什么
And then you're like now I wanna start
an EC2 incidence, what do I wanna do?
你点击发射事件，我不明白。
You click launch incidence,
I don't get this.
所以为了学习，我不会说 AWS 是最好的地方。
So for learning I wouldn't say
AWS is the best place to go.
它的威力更强，而 AWS 的特征比 DigitalOcean 还多。
It's a bit more powerful and
AWS has more features than DigitalOcean.
但学习我们使用的是 DigitalOcean。
But for learning we're using DigitalOcean.
这就是为什么，给你我的推理。
That's why,
give you my reasoning yet things.
所以我们想做的是从 Droplet开始。
So what we wanna do is get
started with the Droplets.
因此，只需单击 " 入门 " ，他们就会启动动画。
So just click Get Started with a Droplet,
they will start animation.
现在你得选择一个形象
And now you have to choose an image.
映像是基本操作系统的副本。
An image is a copy of a base OS.
因此，基线操作系统和基线不同类型的 CPU 计算。
So a baseline operating system and
baseline different types of CPU compute.
你不用创建一个项目
You don't have to create a project,
如果您还想单击 " 创建 " 小滴，那么可以创建一个小滴。
you can just create a droplet if you
wanna also click Create droplet.
Droplet 是他们的想法，很容易使用 VPS。
A droplet is their idea is stick
with an easy to use the VPS.
那部分不重要但问题是安瓦尔
That part doesn't matter but
good question, Anwar.
在他们的屏幕上看这个的人看起来不像这样。
And anybody watching this in their
screen doesn't quite look like this.
解决方案可能会更改其 UI。
Dissolution may change up their UI.
我不知道他们能为我所知道的一切做 AB 测试
I don't know they could be
running AB test for all I know.
但别担心这个
But don't worry about that.
只要听听我们在说什么的底线就好了
Just listen to kind of the baseline of
what we're saying and just follow along.
又来了， DigitalOcean 有个不错的 UI，很好，闪闪发亮。
Cuz again, DigitalOcean they have
a nice UI, it's nice and shiny.
我们想选择的是我们想选择 Ubuntu
What we wanna choose is
we wanna choose Ubuntu,
这将成为默认的默认值。
which is going to be
the default one chosen.
我们想确保我们在 LTS 版本上而不是上面
And we wanna make sure we're on the LTS
version and not the one above and
不是下面的原因，因为命令的工作方式将略有不同
not the one below, because the commands
will work slightly differently
取决于 Ubuntu的版本。
depending on the version of Ubuntu.